Guide to the Feminist Women's Health Center Records, 1973-2003 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Files Series, 1974-2002 and undated, (20 boxes)
  - General Administrative Files, 1974-2002, (16 boxes)
    - Turner, Metropolitan, Komen grants, 1996 (Box 13)
    - Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), 2002 Aug (Box 13)
    - Annual Report, 1999-2000 (Box 13)
    - Support group manual, 1995 Oct (Box 13)
    - Prenatal care and delivery referrals (Box 13)
    - MACF grants, 1994-1997 (Box 13)
    - HIV prevention counseling precourse, 1997 (Box 13)
    - Phone number list staff (Box 13)
    - The Population Council, 1995 Mar 29 (Box 13)
    - Battered women services (Box 13)
    - Referral lists (Box 13)
    - Memorandum, 1988-1989, Randall Terry (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous human resources (Box 14)
    - Volunteer recruitment/training (Box 14)
    - Surgical supplies (Box 14)
    - NAF clinical policy guidelines, 1997 (Box 14)
    - Training of trainers (Box 14)
    - State of Georgia Health Planning Agency, 1994-2000, (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Fees (Box 15)
    - Substance abuse policy (Box 15)
    - Strategic planning, 1998 (Box 15)
    - Department of Human Resources (Box 15)
    - Sentinel Digital Technologies (Box 15)
    - International women's shelters (Box 15)
    - Petty cash/office supplies (Box 15)
    - New building (Box 15)
    - Cambodian forms (Box 15)
    - Counseling forms (Box 15)
    - Sonogram contracts (Box 15)
    - Management (Box 15)
    - Grants (Box 15)
    - Policy and procedure (Box 15)
    - Emergency protocol in service, 2000 Jul 26 (Box 15)
    - Women in need funds, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Annual clinic report, 1992 (Box 15)
    - Business plan, 1992 (Box 15)
    - Teen program, 1993 (Box 15)
    - Clinic quick reference (Box 15)
    - Lobbying materials (Box 15)
    - Thank-you cards, 2003 and undated (Box 15)
    - OSHA manual, (3 folders) (Box 16)
    - Marketing (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16)
    - IRL Lab prices (Box 16)
    - HIV antibody testing protocols (Box 16)
    - Promotional material, 1995 (Box 16)
    - HIV testing consent (Box 16)
    - Projects/progress reports (Box 16)
  - Meetings, 1978-2002, (4 boxes)
    Contains files documenting the range of regular meetings held by the FWHC, including daily meetings following clinic hours, monthly staff meetings, and yearly meetings of the Center's Board of Directors, as well as meetings of various committees of the Center.
    RESTRICTION: Most files related to daily staff meetings and all notes from Board of Directors meetings have been physically relocated to the Closed Series and are closed to research.
    - Annual meeting, 1978 (Box 17)
    - Annual meeting- personnel report, 1982-1983 (Box 17)
    - Annual meeting, 1983 (Box 17)
    - Annual meeting, 1984 (Box 17)
    - Annual meeting, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Annual meeting, 1986 (Box 17)
    - Annual meeting, 1987 (Box 17)
    - Annual meeting, 1988 (Box 17)
    - Annual meeting, 1989 (Box 17)
    - Annual meeting, 1990 (Box 17)
    - Annual meeting, 1992 (Box 17)
    - Annual meeting, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Board of Directors ballot results, 1989 Apr 17 (Box 17)
    - Committees, 1991-1992 (Box 17)
    - Director's meeting, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - Executive Committee meeting, 1990 Feb 21 (Box 18)
    - Executive Committee meeting, 1990 May 18 (Box 18)
    - Executive Committee meeting, 1991 Mar (Box 18)
    - Executive Committee meeting, 1992 Feb 18 (Box 18)
    - Executive Committee meeting- Board of Directors, 1992 Jun 22 (Box 18)
    - Federation meeting, 1986 Oct (Box 18)
    - Finance Committee (Box 18)
    - Fundraising Committee (Box 18)
    - Long range planning (Box 18)
    - Long range planning, 1991 Feb 5 (Box 18)
    - Long range planning, 1991 Sept 9 (Box 18)
    - Long range planning, 1992 Nov (Box 18)
    - Management meeting, 1992 (Box 18)
    - Monthly meetings, 1986 (Box 18)
    - Monthly meetings, 1987 (Box 18)
    - Monthly meetings, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - Monthly meetings, 1989 (Box 18)
    - Monthly meetings, 1990 (Box 18)
    - Monthly meetings, 1991 (Box 19)
    - Monthly meetings, 1992 (Box 19)
    - Monthly meetings, 1993 (Box 19)
    - Nominating Committee, 1993 Mar 15 (Box 19)
    - Personnel Committee (Box 19)
    - Quality Assurance Committee (Box 19)
    - Quality Assurance Committee- chart review, 1987-1993 (Box 19)
    - Quality Assurance Committee meeting, 1991 May (Box 19)
    - Quality Assurance Committee meeting, 1991 Sept (Box 19)
    - Quality Assurance Committee meeting, 1992 Mar (Box 19)
    - Quality Assurance Committee meeting, 1992 Sept 18 (Box 19)
    - Quality Assurance Committee meeting, 1993 (Box 19)
    - Quality Assurance Committee meeting, 1993 Feb 17 (Box 19)
    - Quality Assurance Committee meeting, 1993 May (Box 19)
    - Womancare annual meeting, 1990 (Box 19)
    - Staff meetings, 1998-1999, (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - Personnel Files, 1982-1995, (1 box)
    Of interest in these files is the documentation of the specific training and orientation Center employees were given. Also contains personnel manuals, including one which details a feminist approach to personnel.
    - Clinic Supervisor job description, interview (Box 20, continued)
    - Personnel manual, 1984, (3 folders) (Box 20, continued)
    - Personnel: A Radical Feminist Approach, 1983 (Box 20, continued)
  - Schedules, 1990-2002, (4 boxes) (Box 20, continued)
    Consists of schedules maintained by staff of the FWHC between the years 1990 and 2002. These files depict the various staff members of the FWHC, from volunteers to physicians, and the coordination required to provide offered services.
    CLOSED: All materials from this subseries are currently located in the Closed Series and are CLOSED to research.
- Clinic Files Series, 1980-2002 and undated, (29 boxes)
  Materials in this series include a range of records related to clinical services provided and research studies conducted at the Feminist Women's Health Center (FWHC).
  This series has been divided into four subseries: Statistics, Laboratory Statistics, Research, and Patient Education Information.
  - Statistics, 1981-2002, (12 boxes)
    The FWHC was required to maintain extensive statistics and records related to services provided. Data collected included details about abortions performed, medications kept and used at the center, and equipment maintenance and cleaning. A significant portion of these statistics were collected for the National Abortion Federation.
    Files are arranged primarily in alphabetical order, with chronological arrangement where applicable.
    - Abortion statistics, 1996 (Box 20, continued)
    - Abortion statistics June 30-Aug 2 1997, (5 folders) (Box 20, continued)
    - Abortion stats Aug 4-9 1997 (Box 21)
    - Abortion statistics 1998 (Box 21)
    - Abortion statistics, 1999, (2 folders) (Box 21)
    - Abortion statistics, 2000, (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Age distribution, 1988 Jan-1990 Apr, (7 folders) (Box 22)
    - Age distribution, 1990 May-Dec, (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Complications, 1981-1990 Aug, (14 folders) (Box 23)
    - Complications 1990 Sept-1991 (Box 23)
    - Complications 1992-1998, (4 folders) (Box 24)
    - Drug counts, 1990-1993, (2 folders) (Box 24)
    - Emergency drill log (Box 24)
    - Equipment maintenance log (Box 24)
    - Equipment maintenance log- autoclave, 1979-2002, (3 folders) (Box 24)
    - Gestational age study, 1997, (4 folders) (Box 25)
    - Instrument cleaning log, 1997-1999 (Box 25)
    - Narcotics log, 1989-1990 (Box 25)
    - Narcotics log, 1998 (Box 25)
    - NAF log, 1988 Jan-Apr (Box 25)
    - NAF log, 1988 May-1990 Dec, (8 folders) (Box 26)
    - NAF log, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - NAF log, 1998-2000 Jun, (5 folders) (Box 27)
    - NAF log, 2000 Jul-2001, (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 27)
    - NAF log 2001, (Folders 2-3 of 3) (Box 28)
    - NAF log 2002, (3 folders) (Box 28)
    - Pathology log, 1991-1992 (Box 28)
    - Pathology log, 1996 Jan-Apr (Box 28)
    - Pathology log, 1996 May-Dec (Box 28)
    - Pathology log, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - Pathology log, 2000 (Box 29)
    - Supply log, 1996-2002, (7 folders) (Box 29)
    - Weekly drug control log, 2001 (Box 29)
    - Evaluation reports/results received, 1998 (Box 30)
    - Proficiency testing- plan of correction, 1994-1995 (Box 30)
    - Lab deviation reports, 1994-1996, (4 folders) (Box 30)
    - Lab deviation reports, 1997-2000, (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Plan of correction, 1996-2001 (Box 31)
    - Emergency protocol meeting, 2002 (Box 31)
    - Clinical laboratory improvement amendments (CLIA) archives, 1996 (Box 31)
    - American Proficiency Institute evaluations, 1998-2002, (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - OSHA surveillance, 1992-1997, (5 folders) (Box 31)
    - Abortion services in the United States, 1984-1985 (Box 31)
    - Blank forms (Box 31)
    - Statistics, 1993 (Box 31)
    - Abortion quality indicators (Box 31)
    - Q-Care revision (Box 31)
    - Meeting forms (Box 31)
    - Infection control quality (Box 31)
    - IV therapy (Box 31)
    - Well-Woman quality (Box 31)
    - NAF statistics forms (Box 31)
    - CRAE reports (Box 31)
    - Individual/work group proposal (Box 31)
    - OSHA: surveillance review packets (Box 31)
    - Research (Box 31)
    - Diversity seminar at National Association of Social Workers (NASW) (Box 31)
    - Abortion- action alert notices (Box 31)
    - Women's center service approach (in service) (Box 31)
    - Abortion consulting materials (Box 31)
    - Sexual trauma counseling (Box 31)
    - Planned Parenthood, "What to Do If I'm Pregnant?" (Box 31)
    - Birth control information (Box 31)
    - Gestational age study (Box 31)
    - Follow up appointments: NAF (Box 31)
    - Gestational age study correspondence (Box 31)
    - Insurance 1099 Forms (Box 31)
    - Film donations, 1996 (Box 31)
  - Laboratory Statistics, 1988-1999, (1 box)
    Includes (anonymous) laboratory results of tests performed on clinic patients during a certain time period. These files represent the record-keeping practices of the FWHC and indicate the number of patients typically treated by the FWHC as well.
    Arrangement is alphabetical by folder title.
    - Vital statistics tally, 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box 32)
    - Well-Woman statistics, 1988 (Box 32)
    - Well-Woman statistics, 1999 (Box 32)
  - Research Files, 1980-2001, (15 boxes)
    Two large-scale studies including patients of the FWHC as participants were conducted at the Center and are documented in this collection. One of these studies investigated the use of cervical caps as a method of contraception and the other investigated the use of mifepristone and misoprostol (M&M) to medically induce abortion.
    - Cervical Cap Study, 1980-1988, (11 boxes)
      The FWHC carried out a study over a period of 9 years on the use of cervical caps. Extensive files in this subseries document the protocols of the study, research conducted about various types of cervical caps, yearly reports, and correspondence. A significant number of survey response cards completed anonymously by participants are also included.
      Portions of this subseries are arranged alphabetically or are grouped by similar topic or year. Researchers are encouraged to browse folder title lists.
      - Cervical cap packet originals (Box 32, continued)
      - Cervical cap studies (Box 32, continued)
      - FWHC correspondence (Box 32, continued)
      - Cap price breakdown (Box 32, continued)
      - Self help group site agreements (Box 32, continued)
      - General correspondence with self help groups (Box 32, continued)
      - Forms for self help group use (Box 32, continued)
      - Letter to self help groups re: paperwork planning (Box 32, continued)
      - Sample caps (Box 32, continued)
      - Slide show script (Box 32, continued)
      - Cap symposium (Box 32, continued)
      - People to invite to symposium (Box 32, continued)
      - Summary of preliminary cap study results (Box 32, continued)
      - Continuing education credit (Box 32, continued)
      - Letters to cervical cap inquiries (Box 32, continued)
      - Protocol for cap follow up exam (Box 32, continued)
      - Letter to Gerald Bernstein (Box 32, continued)
      - Portland coordination information (Box 32, continued)
      - Health research group correspondence (Box 32, continued)
      - WWHS correspondence (Box 32, continued)
      - Grid sheet information (Box 32, continued)
      - Original short grid and explanation (Box 32, continued)
      - Cap survey information (Box 32, continued)
      - Investigator agreement forms (Box 32, continued)
      - Investigator resume (Box 32, continued)
      - Key contact people (Box 32, continued)
      - Caps ordered and sent (Box 32, continued)
      - Peggy's proposal (Box 32, continued)
      - Requests for cap providing information (Box 32, continued)
      - Sea sponges (Box 32, continued)
      - Womancare lawsuit (Box 32, continued)
      - Cap three month questionnaire (Box 33)
      - Cervical cap reports (Box 33)
      - Conference call reports (Box 33)
      - Monthly cap reports (Box 33)
      - Reports from trip to Washington, 1980 Nov (Box 33)
      - Cap inventory, 1987 Jul-1988 Sept (Box 33)
      - Cap log for self help group orders (Box 33)
      - Annual cervical cap study report, 1983 (Box 33)
      - Record lists (Box 33)
      - Downtown PS reports (Box 33)
      - Food and Drug Administration (FDA) audit (Box 33)
      - Release notices (Box 33)
      - PMA (Box 33)
      - FWHC protocols (Box 33)
      - Original copy of application for investigational device exemption (Box 33)
      - Protocols (Box 33)
      - Conditional acceptance of protocol (Box 33)
      - FDA and advertising (Box 33)
      - FDA and age (Box 33)
      - FDA consent information (Box 33)
      - FDA annual report proposal (Box 33)
      - FDA statistics proposal (Box 33)
      - Investigational Device Exemption (IDE) approval letter (Box 33)
      - Medical device amendments (Box 33)
      - Medical device listing (Box 33)
      - Institutional Review Board (IRB) meeting agendas (Box 33)
      - Self help IRB information (Box 33)
      - Correspondence with IRB (Box 33)
      - Letters to IRB re: first cap report (Box 33)
      - IRB- to go to FDA (Box 33)
      - Correspondence (Box 33)
      - Correspondence with Lamberts (Box 33)
      - Customs (Box 33)
      - Consent form, 1983 Mar (Box 33)
      - Other cap providers (Box 33)
      - Letters to Lillian Yin (Box 33)
      - Originals- cap material (Box 33)
      - Cap study, 1982 (Box 33)
      - Summary of cap study (Box 33)
      - Annual cap report, 1982 (Box 33)
      - Cap study- to be retyped (Box 33)
      - Letter to cap groups re: first three month study (Box 33)
      - Results sheet and information (Box 33)
      - Statistics on cap, 1982 (Box 33)
      - Yakima cap tour letter and list (Box 33)
      - Annual report grids, 1981-1982, (2 folders) (Box 34)
      - Cap diagrams and letter for groups (Box 34)
      - Cap illustrations (Box 34)
      - Johan Eliot, M.D.- Ann Arbor Community Health (Box 34)
      - Actinomyces (Box 34)
      - Business reply mail InfoCap bibliography (Box 34)
      - Cap/diaphragm without jelly paper (Box 34)
      - Cap providers (Box 34)
      - Cap suggestions (Box 34)
      - Emma Goldman cap study (Box 34)
      - History of cap (Box 34)
      - Inmed (Box 34)
      - James Koch, M.D.- Cap instructions (Box 34)
      - National Women's Health Network (NWHN) cap information (Box 34)
      - Cervical cap problems guide (Box 34)
      - Reclassifying the cap (Box 34)
      - Self help group addresses and correspondence (Box 34)
      - Consent form (Box 34)
      - Authorization and consent for laminaria insertion (Box 34)
      - Haffner, Marlene correspondence (Box 34)
      - Lamberts correspondence (Box 34)
      - Protocol (Box 34)
      - Questionnaire (Box 34)
      - Disposable diaphragm study (Box 34)
      - Instructions for use (Box 34)
      - Statement of investigator (Box 34)
      - Device inventory sheet (Box 34)
      - Daily record (Box 34)
      - Informed consent (Box 34)
      - IRB approval (Box 34)
      - Letters from Joanne Kompare (Box 34)
      - Letters to Joanne Kompare (Box 34)
      - Physician's brochure (Box 34)
      - Slide originals (Box 34)
      - Vimule audit (Box 34)
      - Witt, Ann- letters to (Box 34)
      - Yin, Lillian meeting, 1987 Jun 10 (Box 34)
      - Cervical cap study report, 1982 (Box 34)
      - Cervical cap study report, 1983 (Box 34)
      - Cervical cap study report, 1984 (Box 34)
      - Application for IDE (Box 34)
      - Cap information (Box 35)
      - FDA- letters from (Box 35)
      - FDA- letters to (Box 35)
      - Cap packet (Box 35)
      - Cap press releases (Box 35)
      - Cervical cap provider (Box 35)
      - Cap report- blank (Box 35)
      - Cap report, 1984 (Box 35)
      - Cap self help groups- list of (Box 35)
      - Cap study (Box 35)
      - Cap study, 1985 (Box 35)
      - Cap study, 1986 (Box 35)
      - Cap symposium report (Box 35)
      - Cervical cap fitting training program (Box 35)
      - Cervical cap and pap smear results (Box 35)
      - Cervical cap- use effectiveness study (quarterly report) (Box 35)
      - Cervical cap annual report, 1986 (Box 35)
      - Dumas cervical cap, revised 1988 Jul 28, (2 folders) (Box 35)
      - Goldman, Emma- cervical cap study (Box 35)
      - Federal registers (Box 35)
      - Letters regarding self help groups and IRB (Box 35)
      - IDE no waiver from FDA (Box 35)
      - IRB (Box 35)
      - National cervical cap advisory committee (Box 36)
      - Preliminary cap findings- FWHC (Box 36)
      - Summerhayes, Liz- letter from (Box 36)
      - Vimule cap chronology of events (Box 36)
      - Vimule cap follow up sheets (Box 36)
      - Vimule hearing transcripts, (3 folders) (Box 36)
      - Vimule hearing typesetting (Box 36)
      - Vimule pilot study (Box 36)
      - Vimule study reports (Box 36)
      - Vimule testimony- FWHC (Box 36)
      - Cervical cap advertisement (Box 36)
      - Cervical Cap Ltd. (Box 36)
      - Cap committee meeting (Box 36)
      - Cap East coast meeting (Box 36)
      - Cervical cap FDA approval (Box 36)
      - FDA- obligations of sponsors and monitors in clinical investigations (Box 36)
      - Cap form letter (Box 36)
      - Cervical cap found effective (Box 36)
      - Cervical cap fitters associates (Box 36)
      - Cervical cap guide- Harper and Row, 1987 (Box 36)
      - Application for an IDE (Box 36)
      - Annual cervical cap study report, 1983 (Box 36)
      - Cervical cap study, 1985 (Box 36)
      - Cervical cap study, 1987 (Box 36)
      - Totals for all Feminist Women's Health Centers participating in joint vimule cap study (Box 37)
      - Vimule cap progress report summary findings (Box 37)
      - Bioresearch reporting ETR review (Box 37)
      - New England Journal of Medicine (Box 37)
      - Various correspondence (Box 37)
      - List of government exhibits (Box 37)
      - Use of cervical caps at the University of California at Berkeley (Box 37)
      - Studies of cervical caps: vaginal lesions associated with use of vimule cap (Box 37)
      - New developments in vaginal contraception (Box 37)
      - Application for an IDE (Box 37)
      - The effects of prolonged retention of diaphragms on colonization on Staphylococcus in the lower genital tract (Box 37)
      - Barrier contraception: a comprehensive overview (Box 37)
      - Toxic shock syndrome (Box 37)
      - Prentif cervical cap: acceptability aspects and their implications for future cap design (Box 37)
      - The Prentif contraceptive cervical cap: a contemporary study of its clinical safety and effectiveness (Box 37)
      - FemCap budget (Box 37)
      - Women interested in FemCap (Box 37)
      - Cap study, 1988 (Box 37)
      - Cervical cap: principles and practice (Box 37)
      - Cervical cap as a method of birth control (Box 37)
      - Cap study procedures (Box 37)
      - Cervical cap study report, 1987 (Box 37)
      - Cervical cap study, 1987 (Box 37)
      - Winning in Connecticut (Box 37)
      - Contraceptive research and development program (Box 37)
      - Lea's Shield (Box 37)
      - Lea's Shield study (Box 37)
      - Survey response cards, (6 folders) (Box 38)
      - Survey response cards, (7 folders) (Box 39)
      - Survey response cards, (7 folders) (Box 40)
      - Survey response cards, (7 folders) (Box 41)
      - Survey response cards, (9 folders) (Box 42)
    - Mifepristone and Misoprostol Study, 1994-2000 and undated, (4 boxes)
      Contains files related to a study of the drugs Mifepristone and Misoprostol conducted at the FWHC. These drugs, also known under the brand name Mifeprex or as RU-486, can be used in conjunction as a form of early abortion. Materials include study protocols, results, forms and information given to participants, and other related information.
      - Drug Enforcement Administration (DEA) application (Box 43)
      - DEA regulations (Box 43)
      - Certificate of Need (Box 43)
      - Certificate of Need guidelines (Box 43)
      - Strategic planning (Box 43)
      - Clinic statements (Box 43)
      - Clinic tally sheets (Box 43)
      - Beijing (Box 43)
      - Bylaws, 1996 (Box 43)
      - Budget, 1996 (Box 43)
      - Security (Box 43)
      - Lighting (Box 43)
      - GA for Choice grants (Box 43)
      - Turner Foundation grants (Box 43)
      - State planning agency tally sheets, 1994-1995 (Box 43)
      - Metropolitan grant (Box 43)
      - Grants, 1996 (Box 43)
      - Study protocols, forms, 2000 (Box 43)
      - Miscellaneous articles (Box 43)
      - Randomized consent/packet/chart (Box 43)
      - RU-486 (Box 43)
      - Weekly drug control logs (Box 44)
      - DHR new (Box 44)
      - DHR 1980 clinic inspection (Box 44)
      - DHR 1993 (Box 44)
      - DHR report, 1996 (Box 44)
      - ABM surgery center survey (Box 44)
      - Licensure inspection (Box 44)
      - Statistics (Box 44)
      - Laminaria guidelines (Box 44)
      - Sample bylaws/applications/peer review (Box 44)
      - Mission statement (Box 44)
      - Stock medications (Box 44)
      - MSOS, 1995 (Box 44)
      - Medical bylaws, 1995 (Box 44)
      - Mission statement (Box 44)
      - Face to Face (Box 44)
      - Mifepristone and Misoprostol (M&M) info, (4 folders) (Box 45)
      - Health worker telephone script (Box 45)
      - M&M/clinic defense (Box 45)
      - Random M&M trial- Misoprostol randomized to 24, 48, & 72 Hours (Box 45)
      - Random M&M study- Misoprostol randomized oral/vaginal at 24 hours (up to 63 days): STUDY F, (2 folders) (Box 45)
      - Vaginal ultrasound information: STUDY J, (2 folders) (Box 45)
      - STUDY A, (4 folders) (Box 46)
      - Communications: STUDY L (Box 46)
      - Consent forms/education pamphlet (Box 46)
      - Adverse events (Box 46)
      - WIRB approvals (Box 46)
      - M&M pathology log, 1995 (Box 46)
      - M&M study information, 1995, (2 folders) (Box 46)
      - M&M study information, 1998 (Box 46)
      - M&M (Box 46)
      - M&M vaginal/oral health charts (Box 46)
      - Sample patient chart (Box 46)
      - Investigator information questionnaire, 1997 (Box 46)
  - Patient Education Information, undated, (2 boxes)
    Consists of fact sheets related to women's health and information about services provided by the FWHC. These items were made available to patients of the Center.
    Arranged alphabetically.
    - Abortion fact sheets (Box 47)
    - Abortion fees (Box 47)
    - Abortion news (Box 47)
    - Adoption referrals (Box 47)
    - Advanced cardiac life support information (Box 47)
    - After care information (Box 47)
    - AIDS (Box 47)
    - Allergies (Box 47)
    - Anemia (Box 47)